Friends, in this video you will learn how
you will be
able to get your scooter or bike insured sitting at home in just 2 minutes through Paytm. Also,
friends, you should watch the entire video so that I will
tell you one of my secret tips here, through which guys, I always get
my scooter or bike insured
and I have four to five years of experience
in this field and guys, I have
two bikes and one scooter which
I always get insured,
I get more benefits at a lower price,
so I will share a tip with you too,
just watch the video carefully and completely
so that you can get complete information,
first of all
you will see an insurance section on your mobile phone, so
here you can see, in insurance
you will see many different types of insurance
like car insurance, bike
insurance, apart from this there is health
insurance and many more, so right now
we have to go to bike insurance,
so we have to click on bike insurance,
if you do not see it here then you will
see a search icon above, you simply have to
click on the search icon and
here you have to write bike, as you
will search for bike insurance,  Here you will
see bike insurance, you have to click on it,
after clicking a page will open in front of you like this,
now guys you will
see below, here you have to enter the number of your vehicle,
scooter or bike,
after that you have to
click on get quit here, now
guys a page has opened here and it is being
told here which company your vehicle belongs to,
how many CC it is,
what is the registration date, if all your information is correct
then it is fine, if not then you will
click on incorrect details here
and you will check your details once
from your RC and you will do it,
after that you will have to select here, yes it is
my vehicle,
as soon as you select it, another
page will open in front of you, at the top you will see
assisting policy details, that is,
our insurance policy which is running right now has
not ended yet, two days are left for it to end,
so here you
get NCB which is called no claim bonus,
50% is given here and here
Guys, let me tell you that there are two types of
insurance policies. First
is comprehensive, which we
also call first party insurance. Now,
what will happen here, God forbid, if your car ever meets with an
accident, then in this condition,
whatever damage is caused to your car, the
insurance policy company will definitely provide it.
Along with that,
whatever damage is caused to the person in front, the
insurance policy will also provide it. Okay, so
you have to keep this in mind, that is,
everything is covered in comprehensive,
which we also call first party.
Both are the same thing. Now the second one is the
third party here. Now, friends, the meaning of third party is that
suppose
your car met with an accident, you
hit someone's car. Now, what will happen in that condition, the
damage caused to your car, the
insurance policy will not provide it,
but the person in front, who is the
third party, will get the full benefit of the
insurance policy,
you have to keep this in mind and if I
talk about pricing, then hardly ₹1  There is a difference of ₹50 to ₹2000000,
so you always have to get a
comprehensive policy,
you have to keep this in mind especially and right now you will
see that here in total six
companies are listed in comprehensive and here
five companies are listed in third party, so right now
we have to do comprehensive as well and
you will see many companies here
now guys see here there are different companies
whichever you find right, now you will see the price is
also different here, the reason for this is that
here your vehicle has an IDV
value, that is, let us
assume the insured declared value, if your
vehicle gets stolen or your vehicle catches
fire, then in that condition the company which you are getting
insured, how much
money will it pay you, that is called
IDV value, so you have to
understand it completely, it is very easy to understand and guys
see here like here there is IFFCO Tokio
company, if you pay ₹10.5 then
you will get ₹1.1415 here  Here you will
get your IDV value. Apart from this, there is a
policy here of The New India
Insurance Company. It is being told here
that for ₹1,166 you get a value of ₹1,749. There are
different policies, but
guys, here one insurance is
not listed here. Now guys, here, as
I told you, I
always use secret tips, so I will give you this secret
tip that you should always get
your insurance done from one insurance company because guys,
I have been getting my scooter and bike insurance done for the last four to five years.
And I have
made a complete video on how to get it done. If you want to
watch it, you will get the link in the description of the video.
You must watch that video later.
Because what happens here
in one insurance is that you can increase
or decrease the IDV value of your vehicle.
Apart from this,
you get more benefits at a lower price there.
Because I am able to
compare here, that is why I am giving you
this advice.  I am waiting guys, okay, so
for now let's see which one we have to do, let's say let's
see here two
insurance policies, for ₹10.5 here we are
getting a value of ₹10 and for ₹1.1416
here we are getting ₹1.749,
only here it is hardly how much
rupees, see here we are getting 3 to 00
extra, okay, so let's do it
brother,
we have selected the amount here from The New India Insurance Company,
now it is telling here that
which
insurance policy of yours which was running for you, has it
ended, okay, so you have to
select the name of the company here,
like our IFFCO was running, we have
selected it here and friends, please
tell me quickly by commenting,
which company's insurance policy was yours
and which bike or scooter do you have,
please do tell us by commenting  Okay, and after that
you will come down, all the details are given here,
you simply have to do what is done here,
after doing what is done, you are being asked here
that did you make a claim in the
assisting policy, that is, did you get any
claim passed
from the insurance in the previous policy, if we did not get anything done here, then
we will say no, if you did it, then
you can say yes, so like we did no,
after this you have to select 50 here
and you have to click proceed here,
as soon as you do it,
now you have to wait a little here, now guys, it is being
told here in whose
name this RC is here, that is, in
whose name the vehicle is,
some things are hidden here
due to security reasons, now you have to get
KYC done here, so for that,
guys, see here the PAN number is visible,
if you click on it, you will be
able to get your KYC done with your Aadhaar number, so let us select the PAN number here,
we have selected it
Now you will have to enter your PAN number in this box below,
below that you will have to select your date of birth,
date, month, year. Now whether it is male or female,
you can select it here, apart from that, if
you have added your communication address, it will be
visible in it. If you
want to add it, then you will update your address by adding a new address
here. Apart from that, you will
add the nominee here. For example, if
you want to make a nominee, you will enter their name,
what is their age, what is your
relation with them, after that, when you come down here, the
details of your vehicle will be visible,
like what is the engine number, what is the chase number,
now if you have a loan on your vehicle, then it is
visible here that there is no loan, it is selected on no,
and here it is telling that
which company was your previous insurance from, so
we had selected it, and here
you will have to enter your assisting policy number,
okay guys, your
old policy number will be written on it,
so look there and
enter it here, after this friends,
you will see a box below here,
You will tick and after ticking,
if you want to see the price breakup here, how much is the
insurance,
how much GST is being charged, what are the things, then
here you click on the price breakup
and see here, like our basic on
damage is ₹ 1000000, third party
insurance is worth this much,
how much discount is received here and how much GST is charged
and what is the total amount, okay, so let
us cut it, now we will proceed
to pay, okay, as you
click on proceed to pay, you will have to
wait a little here, now you will have to make
your payment here, now
how do you want to make the payment, the
option of paytm2 is coming, if you want, you
can also do it through EMI here, debit
card, credit card, UPI, net banking,
you get all the options, so now at
present,
if you download the policy from our paytmfirstgames.com, you will be
able to do two wheeler insurance by using paytm-in app and friends, to
support us, please like the video and
share it with your friends